Savkin Nikita

Front-end Developer

+7(906)041-42-85

├── no.colour.you.like@gmail.com

♠ no-colour-you-like.github.io

ຶ່ງເກີງ linkedin.com/in/nikitasavkin

Skills

Programming languages

JavaScript (ES6+), TypeScript, HTML, CSS (SASS, SCSS)

Libraries & Frameworks

React, Redux

Additional

Git, GitHub, npm, BEM, responsive design, debugging

Projects

E-commerce store

Website for a store that sells plants.

React | Redux | Firebase

https://no-colour-you-like.github.io/plantse-commerce/

Cryptocurrency tracker

Tracking cryptocurrency in real time.

JavaScript | API | Chart.js

https://no-colour-you-like.github.io/Crypto

Movies Navigation

Navigation with popular movie lists.

JavaScript | API

https://no-colour-you-like.github.io/Movies

Launcher Inc

Website about a rocket engine testing company.

HTML | CSS (SASS) | JavaScript

https://no-colour-you-like.github.io/Launcher

Languages

Russian - Native

English - Pre-intermediate

Soft Skills

Critical thinking

Adaptability and flexibility

Teamwork

Profile

I'm a Front-end developer specializing in creating unique web applications. I strive to create immersive, beautiful, user-friendly websites and web applications with quality and well-designed code. I'm working on improving interactive design based web applications using animations and smooth transitions. I enjoy challenging myself and doing interesting, challenging and important tasks. I actively continue to develop my skills not only towards the Front-end, but also towards the Back-end.



Experience

Front-end Developer (Personal websites & web applications)

March 2020 - Present

- Developed and maintained code for client websites primarily using HTML, CSS (SASS) and JavaScript;
- Manually tested sites in various browsers and mobile devices to ensure cross-browser compatibility and responsiveness;
- Wrote modern, performant, maintainable code for websites and web applications.

Achievements: engineered and implemented five adaptive websites, five JavaScript applications and e-commerce project using React.

Store Manager @ GAP

September 2016 - September 2019

- Control of store activities, accountability, selection and training of employee, control and management of personnel, interaction with customers.

Achievements: recruited and trained 20 employees, increased customer loyalty after controversial situations.



Education

The Complete JavaScript Course (Jonas Schmedtmann)

Complete React Developer Course (Andrei Neagoie)

2020 - 2021 // Moscow

Direction: Front-end development

Moscow State University of Mechanical Engineering

2012 - 2016 // Moscow

Degree: Bachelor's degree in management